

CONTACT

- +971 56 371 3350
- ▼ TAYCOvayann@gmail.com
- Dubai, United Arab Emirates
- Filipino

EDUCATION

Apr 2023 - Jan 2024 SUCCESS WISDOM

- Certified Professional Nursing Assistant (720 hours)
- GPA: 97.35

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023 HAYAT INSTITUTE

Caregiver Course (120 hours)

SKILLS

- Empathetic
- Communication
- Keen attention to details
- Team-player
- Creative

LANGUAGES

- English
-
- Filipino
-

VAY-ANN TAYCO

CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT

PROFILE

AA compassionate, trustworthy and dedicated Certified Nursing Assistant with a GPA of 97.35, who is committed to provide quality care and service and to promote a safe and positive patient experience. Possess excellent ability to adapt to different situations with a cheerful attitude, good sense of community, willing to learn and looking forward for an opportunity that will help me enhance my skills and be a valuable asset in that organization that I worked for.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hira Industries LLC, UAE

JAN 2022 - PRESENT

Quality Officer

- Ensuring materials and products meet specifications as per company's standard by conducting thorough inspections and highlights non-conforming products to concerned departments
- Preparation of new sample products for customers and exhibits
- Preparing monthly presentation reports
- Communicating regularly with production coordinator and supervisors for quality-related matters
- Identifying opportunities for process improvement to enhance overall product quality

Oriental Group FZE, UAE

JUL 2020 - DEC 2021

Quality Assurance Coordinator

- Performing quality assessment measures on incoming materials and outgoing products and recording of results in the system
- Rejecting products that failed to meet quality standards and reporting the issue to the supervisor
- Preparing and organizing daily and weekly reports
- Maintaining safety and cleanliness of the laboratory at all times
- Works in a shifting basis and ensures proper handover is done daily

RECOMMENDATION

Chrisyaiv G. Dimalanta

Dean of Professional Diploma Dubai

Success Wisdom Professional and Management Development Training LLC

Phone: +971 54 458 5434